Guide to the Time Inc. Advertising Promotion and Circulation Promotion Files 1922-2004 (bulk, 1923-1989) MS 3009-RG 21
New-York Historical Society
- Life: Advertising Promotion: Master Files: Advertising Scrapbooks, 1971-1974 (Offsite-box 3557, Folder 5-6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: Master Files: Posters, 1978-1988 (Offsite-box 3558, Folder 1-15)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Cooperative Mailings, 1951-1953 (Offsite-box 3560, Folder 1-4)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Inserts, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 3560, Folder 5-8)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Acknowledgements, 1938-1955 (Offsite-box 3560, Folder 9)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Billings, 1936-1958, circa 1964-1968 (Offsite-box 3560, Folder 10-17)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Billings, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 3561, Folder 1-5)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1937-1958 (Offsite-box 3561, Folder 6-27)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1959-1972 (Offsite-box 3562, Folder 1-17)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1937-1947 (Offsite-box 3562, Folder 18-19)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1948-1959 (Offsite-box 3563, Folder 1-16)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1960-1972 (Offsite-box 3564, Folder 1-18)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 3557, Folder 7-10)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1972 (Offsite-box 3565, Folder 1-5)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail Cost Analysis, 1953-1972 (Offsite-box 3565, Folder 6-7)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail Postage Records (Offsite-box 3565, Folder 8)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail Tests, 1948-1953 (Offsite-box 3565, Folder 9-19)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail Tests, 1954-1961 (Offsite-box 3566, Folder 1-16)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail Tests, 1962-1970 (Offsite-box 3567, Folder 1-20)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail Tests [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Offsite-box R55, Folder 51)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail Tests [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R55, Folder 52-53)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail Tests, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 3568, Folder 1-13)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail Tests Results, 1947-1972 (Offsite-box 3569, Folder 1-5)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail Miscellaneous Reports, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 3569, Folder 6)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1937-1950 (Offsite-box 3569, Folder 7-23)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1951-1964 (Offsite-box 3570, Folder 1-18)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1966-1967, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 3571, Folder 1-11)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1971 (Offsite-box 3572, Folder 1-12)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3573, Folder 1-7)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals Report, circa 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 3573, Folder 8)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals Special List, 1971 (Offsite-box 3573, Folder 9)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Saturday Evening Post Fulfillment, 1969 (Offsite-box 3573, Folder 10)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Suspension, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3573, Folder 11-13)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Suspension, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3574, Folder 1-13)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Suspension, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3575, Folder 1-10)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Suspension, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3576, Folder 1-14)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Sweepstakes, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 3577, Folder 1-7)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Sweepstakes Federal Trade Commission Inquiry, 1970 (Offsite-box 3577, Folder 8)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Sweepstakes Prize Winners, 1967-1973 (Offsite-box 3577, Folder 9-11)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Sweepstakes Prize Winners [RESTRICTED], 1967-1973 (Offsite-box R55, Folder 54)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Miscellaneous, 1937-1951 (Offsite-box 3577, Folder 12)
- Life: Circulation Promotion: Miscellaneous, 1947-circa 1967, 1982 (Offsite-box 3577, Folder 13)
- Life International: Advertisers Lists, 1946-1970 (Offsite-box 3578, Folder 1-6)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Ads, 1946-1968 (Offsite-box 3578, Folder 7-3)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Ads: "Life Sells", 1962-1967 (Offsite-box 3578, Folder 14)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Ads: "On Sale", 1966 (Offsite-box 3578, Folder 15)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Advertising Director's Letters, 1961-1967 (Offsite-box 3578, Folder 16)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Direct Mail, 1946-1958 (Offsite-box 3579, Folder 1-14)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Direct Mail, 1950?, 1963-1967 (Offsite-box 3557, Folder 11-12)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Direct Mail, 1959-1967 (Offsite-box 3580, Folder 1-18)
  Includes two English copies and one Japanese translation of The Memoirs of Pablo Casals by Pablo Casals as told to Thomas Dozier, published by Life En Español (1959).
  Includes hardcover English translation of Secret Ceremony by Marco Denevi, First Prize Winner of Life En Español's Literary Contest (1961).
  Includes Communism: The Nature of Your Enemy by John K. Jessup and the editors of Life, 1962.
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports, 1946-1959 (Offsite-box 3581, Folder 1-15)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports, 1959-1966 (Offsite-box 3582, Folder 1-14)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports, 1967-1970, undated (Offsite-box 3583, Folder 1-5)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: Asia, 1966 (Offsite-box 3583, Folder 6)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: Asia, Military, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 3583, Folder 7)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: By Area, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 3583, Folder 8-13)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: Mexico, 1966 (Offsite-box 3583, Folder 14-15)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: Mexico, 1966 (Offsite-box 3584, Folder 1)
- Life International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: Psychographics, 1969 (Offsite-box 3584, Folder 2)
- Life International: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: General, 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 3584, Folder 3)
- Life International: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Life En Español, 1961-1970 (Offsite-box 3584, Folder 4-5)
- Money: Advertising Promotion: General, 1972, 1975-1978 (Offsite-box 3584, Folder 6-9)
- Money: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: Profile of Subscriber Households, 1973 (Offsite-box 3584, Folder 10)
- Money: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: Study of Subscriber Households, 1973 (Offsite-box 3584, Folder 11-12)
- Money: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: House Ads and Inserts, 1973-1976, 1979 (Offsite-box 3584, Folder 13-17)
- Money: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Magazine Inserts, 1972-1979 (Offsite-box 3584, Folder 18-25)
- Money: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Billings, 1974-1979 (Offsite-box 3584, Folder 26-31)
- Money: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3584, Folder 32-34)
- Money: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1975-1980 (Offsite-box 3585, Folder 1-6)
- Money: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1971-1980 (Offsite-box 3585, Folder 7-20)
- Money: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1972-1980 (Offsite-box 3586, Folder 1-9)
- People: Advertising Promotion: General, 1974, 1976-1979, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 3586, Folder 10-20)
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "People Baby Boom Seminar. Lunch. March 8, 1985. Sides A & B. Tape #1."
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "Baby Boomer Seminar. Afternoon. Tape 2 A & B."
- People: Advertising Promotion: General, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3596, Folder 2-3)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Ad Campaign: "The Many Sides of People", 1986 April-1987 February (Offsite-box 3597, Folder 1)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Base Plus Program, 1988 (Offsite-box 3586, Folder 21)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Base Plus Program, 1988 (Offsite-box 3587, Folder 1)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Direct Mail, 1982, 1988 (Offsite-box 3587, Folder 2-3)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: General, 1975 (Offsite-box 3587, Folder 4)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: "A People Partnership: Baby Boomers and 7 Crown", 1985 (Offsite-box 3597, Folder 2)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: Audiences, Compositions and Cost per Thousand (CPM Book), 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 3587, Folder 5-10)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: "Making a Splash: Seagram's Wine Coolers and People", 1985 (Offsite-box 3597, Folder 3)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: People and the Business Magazines, 1987 (Offsite-box 3587, Folder 11)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: People and the Fashion Magazines, 1987 (Offsite-box 3587, Folder 12)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: People and the General Interest Magazines, 1987 (Offsite-box 3587, Folder 13-14)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: People and the Men's Magazines, 1987 (Offsite-box 3587, Folder 15)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: People and the Newsweekly Magazines, 1987 (Offsite-box 3588, Folder 1)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: People and the Women's Service Magazines, 1987 (Offsite-box 3588, Folder 2)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Pre-Publication, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3596, Folder 1)
- People: Advertising Promotion: Rates, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 3588, Folder 3-5)
- People: Circulation Promotion: Newsstand, 1974 (Offsite-box 3588, Folder 6)
- People: Circulation Promotion: Newsstand Circulation Study: "Second Half '74 Cover Analysis: Weekly Magazines", 1974 (Offsite-box 3588, Folder 7-8)
- President: Advertising Promotion: Sampling, 1975-1979 (Offsite-box 3588, Folder 9)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Beginnings, Merchandising Samples (Offsite-box 3596, Folder 4)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Beginnings, Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3596, Folder 5)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Salesmen's Memos (Offsite-box 3588, Folder 10-14)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Salesmen's Memos (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 1-5)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 6)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Convention (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 7)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Memos to Advertisers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 8)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Research, Politz (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 9)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Salesmen's Memos (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 10)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 11)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1956: House Ads and Fillers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 12)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Memos to Advertisers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 13)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1957: House Ads and Fillers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 14)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Memos to Advertisers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 15)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1957-1959: Trade Ads (Offsite-box 3596, Folder 6)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 16)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1958: House Ads and Fillers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 17)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Memos to Advertisers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 18)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1959: House Ads and Fillers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 19)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Memos to Advertisers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 20)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Salesmen's Memos (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 21)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1960: House Ads and Fillers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 22)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Memos to Advertisers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 23)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Salesmen's Memos (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 24)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Trade Ads (Offsite-box 3596, Folder 7)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1960-1963: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 25)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1961: House Ads and Fillers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 26)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Memos to Advertisers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 27)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Trade Ads (Offsite-box 3596, Folder 8)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3596, Folder 9)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Memos to Advertisers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 28)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Salesmen's Memos (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 29)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Trade Ads (Offsite-box 3596, Folder 10)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Memos to Advertisers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 30)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Trade Ads (Offsite-box 3596, Folder 11)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Memos to Advertisers (Offsite-box 3589, Folder 31)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Newsletter (Offsite-box 3590, Folder 1)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Salesmen's Memos (Offsite-box 3590, Folder 2)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Memos to Advertisers (Offsite-box 3590, Folder 3)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Newsletter (Offsite-box 3590, Folder 4)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1968-1973: Memos to Advertisers (Offsite-box 3590, Folder 5)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Memos to Advertisers (Offsite-box 3590, Folder 6)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1978-1980: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3590, Folder 7)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1983: "Since Cortina... Olympics Highlights from 1956 to 1980 through the Eyes of Sports Illustrated" (Offsite-box 3590, Folder 8)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1994: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3596, Folder 12)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: 1995: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3590, Folder 9)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: Ad Reprints, 1965 (Offsite-box 3590, Folder 10-13)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: Master Files: House Ads, 1954-1956 (Offsite-box 3596, Folder 14-15)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: Master Files: House Ads, 1957-1961 (Offsite-box 3598, Folder 1-2)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: Master Files: Trade Ads, 1954-1956 (Offsite-box 3598, Folder 3)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: Master Files: Trade Ads, 1956-1959 (Offsite-box 3599, Folder 1-3)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: Master Files: Trade Ads, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 3600, Folder 1-3)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Promotion: Master Files: Trade Ads, 1961 (Offsite-box 3601, Folder 2)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: House Ads and Inserts, 1954-1966 (Offsite-box 3590, Folder 14-25)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: House Ads and Inserts, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 3591, Folder 1-4)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Inserts, 1954-1974 (Offsite-box 3591, Folder 5-24)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Newsstand, 1954-1956 (Offsite-box 3596, Folder 13)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Space Ads and Inserts, 1957 (Offsite-box 3591, Folder 25)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Tip-ons (Newsstand banner), 1955 (Offsite-box 3591, Folder 26)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Charter Subscriber Certificate, 1955 (Offsite-box 3601, Folder 1)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Billings, 1954-1960, 1965, 1968 (Offsite-box 3591, Folder 27-35)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1954 (Offsite-box 3591, Folder 36)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1957-1972 (Offsite-box 3592, Folder 1-19)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3593, Folder 1-2)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas Billings, 1961, 1963, 1972 (Offsite-box 3593, Folder 3-5)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas Card Samples, 1955-1959 (Offsite-box 3593, Folder 6)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1954-1964, 1968, 1971 (Offsite-box 3593, Folder 7-23)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3594, Folder 1-3)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1954-1961 (Offsite-box 3594, Folder 4-18)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1962-1973 (Offsite-box 3595, Folder 1-9)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Miscellaneous: Books, 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 3595, Folder 10-13)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Miscellaneous: Horan Poster, 1961 (Offsite-box 3595, Folder 14)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Miscellaneous: Subscriber Contest, "Inside Track", 1955 (Offsite-box 3595, Folder 15)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Miscellaneous, 1954, 1982 (Offsite-box 3595, Folder 16)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation Promotion: Miscellaneous: Subscribers Desk Promotion, 1954 (Offsite-box 3595, Folder 17)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1922-1929: General (Offsite-box 3602, Folder 1-2)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1924-1929: General, 1924, 1927-1929 (Offsite-box 3638, Folder 1-3)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1928: General Mail #28-1 - 28-2 (Offsite-box 3602, Folder 3-4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1928: Newsletters (Offsite-box 3602, Folder 5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1929: General Mail #29-3 - 29-12 (Offsite-box 3602, Folder 6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1929: Newsletters (Offsite-box 3602, Folder 7)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1930: General (Offsite-box 3602, Folder 8)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1930: General (Offsite-box 3638, Folder 4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1930: General Mail #30-1 - 30-12 (Offsite-box 3602, Folder 9-11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1930: Newsletters (Offsite-box 3602, Folder 12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1931-1932: General (Offsite-box 3602, Folder 13-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1931: General Mail #31-1 - 31-12 (Offsite-box 3602, Folder 15)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1931: Newsletters (Offsite-box 3602, Folder 16)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1931: General Mail #32-3 - 32-12, 1932 (Offsite-box 3603, Folder 1-2)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1933: Ads (Offsite-box 3603, Folder 3)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1933: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3603, Folder 4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1933: Promotion (Offsite-box 3603, Folder 5-6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1934: Mailings (Offsite-box 3603, Folder 7)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1934: Promotion (Offsite-box 3603, Folder 8-10)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1934: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3603, Folder 11-12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1935: General Mail #35-1 - 35-12 (Offsite-box 3603, Folder 13-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1935: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3603, Folder 15)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1935: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3604, Folder 1)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1935: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3604, Folder 2-3)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1936: General Mail #36-1 - 36-12 (Offsite-box 3604, Folder 4-5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1936: Ads (Offsite-box 3604, Folder 6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1936: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3604, Folder 7)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1937: General Mail #37-1 - 37-12 (Offsite-box 3604, Folder 8-11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1937: General Mail #37-12-C (Offsite-box 3638, Folder 5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1937: Ads (Offsite-box 3604, Folder 12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1937: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3604, Folder 13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1938: General Mail #38-2 - 38-11 (Offsite-box 3604, Folder 14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1938: General Mail #38-12 (Offsite-box 3605, Folder 1-2)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1938: Ads (Offsite-box 3605, Folder 3)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1938: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3605, Folder 4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1939: General Mail #39-1-A (Offsite-box 3638, Folder 6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1939: General Mail #39-6 - 39-12 (Offsite-box 3605, Folder 5-9)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1939: Ads (Offsite-box 3605, Folder 10)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1939: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3605, Folder 11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1940: General Mail #40-1 - 40-12 (Offsite-box 3605, Folder 12-13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1940: General Mail #40-12 (Offsite-box 3638, Folder 7-8)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1940: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3605, Folder 14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1940: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3606, Folder 1)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1941: General Mail #41-1 - 41-12 (Offsite-box 3606, Folder 2-4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1941: General Mail #41-12 (Offsite-box 3638, Folder 9)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1941: Book, The U.S. College Graduate (Offsite-box 3606, Folder 5-6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1941: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3606, Folder 7-8)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1942: General Mail #42-1 - 42-12 (Offsite-box 3606, Folder 9-11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1942: General Mail #42-12 (Offsite-box 3638, Folder 10)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1942: Ads (Offsite-box 3606, Folder 12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1942: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3606, Folder 13-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1943: General Mail #43-1 - 43-12 (Offsite-box 3607, Folder 1-2)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1943: Ads (Offsite-box 3638, Folder 11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1943: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3607, Folder 3-5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1944: General (Offsite-box 3638, Folder 12-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1944: General Mail #44-3 - 44-12 (Offsite-box 3607, Folder 6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1944: Ads (Offsite-box 3638, Folder 15-16)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1944: Direct Mail #3347-3576 (Offsite-box 3607, Folder 7-11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1945: General Mail #45-1 - 45-12 (Offsite-box 3607, Folder 12-13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1945: Ads (Offsite-box 3638, Folder 17-18)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1945: Direct Mail #3577-3857 (Offsite-box 3607, Folder 13-16)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1945: Direct Mail #3858-3946 (Offsite-box 3608, Folder 1-2)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1946: General Mail #46-1 - 46-12 (Offsite-box 3608, Folder 3-4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1946: Ads (Offsite-box 3639, Folder 1-3)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1946: Direct Mail #3952-4266 (Offsite-box 3608, Folder 5-10)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1947: General Mail #47-1 - 47-12 (Offsite-box 3608, Folder 11-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1947: General Mail #47-9-A (Offsite-box 3639, Folder 4)